Your Fault.
-Thank you for coming.
-Ciao.
Those glasses stay here. Thank you.
Hey, it's not
an aphrodisiac cocktail, is it?
When you go up to the room,
you'll see it's not.
-Ciao, Noah.
-Ciao.
Hey, I didn't see Nick!
Yeah, he couldn't come.
He's doing an internship
at a law firm in San Francisco.
And I keep telling his father
not to give him too much work, but...
The glasses.
-What a shame.
-Anyway...
-Ciao, María.
-Have fun.
Your mother's cocktail is disgusting.
Yeah, it tastes like melted candy.
Look, come with me.
The party starts now.
-There you go.
-But only one, okay?
Tomorrow I have to help
Morti and Petra clean up.
For God's sake, let them do their job.
Don't complicate it for the rest of us.
Besides, tomorrow is a holiday!
It's the end of high school.
I don't know if I'll go.
I don't feel like it.
Hey.
What's wrong?
It will soon be a year
since my father's death.
Look at me.
I don't want to see you cry, okay?
He had it coming.
Yeah, I know.
You must stand before him
and say goodbye to him once and for all.
Someday. I promise.
What a shitty year, huh?
I don't know
what I would've done without you.
But I'm not enough for you, am I?
I have hardly seen Nick
all these months, damn it.
I don't even know why I'm taking this.
Because when you do see each other,
all you do is fuck.
You don't waste time.
It's squeezing the most out of time.
You're sure squeezing
the most out of him, right, sweetie?
You extract all his juice.
Come on.
Here's to finally being legal age.
When you can finally do whatever you want,
but you keep doing
what everybody else wants.
You have just invented
the 18-year-old crisis.
The magic pill.
I knew you'd come.
I missed touching you.
I can't tell.
You can't?
You taste like candy.
-I prepared a special cocktail.
-You did?
It's called Noah. Care to try it?
I thought it couldn't get better.
I have been rehearsing a lot. Mentally.
I think you'll be very happy
being 18, Freckles.
Here. Your gift.
What is this?
Nick, it's beautiful.
Here.
I'll wear it forever.
Always.
I just gave you my heart, Freckles.
Please don't break it.
Never.
Hey!
Yours, Noah!
Noah!
The party has already started!
Goodbye, high school!
Come on, girls!
Let's take off our uniforms.
What are you doing here all alone?
We used to burn books.
The guys now are smarter.
They'll invent anything
to get them butt naked.
It's been five years and it shows, huh?
You think?
The other day I asked Jenna
what she wanted for her birthday.
You know what she told me?
That she didn't care,
as long as it's nice outside
so that she can record an unboxing.
When did the wrapping
start being cooler than the gift?
We're getting old, man.
They're unboxing their life
while we are just crumpled wrapping paper.
Don't talk bullshit.
They're going to college.
While we work,
they'll only be thinking about having fun.
We are number one at having fun.
They're off to a dorm
full of people their age.
Don't worry.
Those NPCs are not worth shit.
I mean distance, man.
Noah is staying here while you do
an internship across the pond.
Jenna is going away to medical school,
and I cannot leave the garage.
They're going to fly solo, Nick.
Distance will ruin everything.
Thomas Green.
Noah Morán.
Jenna Tavish.
How are you, bro?
Never better.
Did you meet up with the insurer?
Nope. Impossible.
They won't be sending any more cars.
Sons of bitches.
I am not good, Luca. I can't do this.
-Don't even fucking say that.
-They all ask about you.
When you're not there,
they take their cars elsewhere.
Stay strong, brother.
I'll be out in a year.
I try, but...
I don't think
the garage will last that long.
Actually, I'm not sure
it will even last a month.
Not even a month?
The rent has gone up again.
I screwed up, man. I screwed up.
Listen, asshole.
I screwed up. You didn't, okay?
If we stop sending money,
Mom will start worrying.
Maybe a transfer of ownership--
We're not going to close the garage.
You hear me?
Never.
I don't understand how they can give
those supercars to 18-year-old girls.
These parents have gone crazy.
Stupid spoiled brats.
Wow, looks like
you've spoiled the surprise.
-No.
-Yes.
Oh, my God!
I can't believe it!
Congratulations, nerd.
It's beautiful. This is crazy! But...
No, no. I shouldn't. No way.
Dude, 18-inch alloy wheels.
LED lights! I love it!
I love it.
Wow.
I want to tell you something.
Tell me.
I have been thinking about it for a while.
Fuck, don't go so fast, please.
Don't be a pussy.
We have been hiding for almost a year.
I am sick of tiptoeing down the hall,
and doing it in the garden.
On top of everything, your mother
has assigned Martín to spy on us.
-It was your father.
-No, sorry.
She's the one controlling us all day.
Your father asked. Morti told me.
Fine.
-It's all the same.
-It's not the same. But go on.
Fuck, can you stop? You'll get us killed.
You've become such a bore when you drive.
I want to show you something.
So? What do you think?
Well, it's amazing.
The rent has to be obscene, right?
I don't know.
It's a gift from my grandfather.
-Nick, you can't accept it.
-And you can't accept that car.
I know.
It's a bitch to live
with contradictions, isn't it?
Especially if you're rich.
I'm not going back to San Francisco.
That's going to kill my mother.
To be an intern, I'd rather stay here.
I hate being away from you, Freckles.
Plus, look at this light.
It's perfect for us.
Us?
Yes.
And it's close to the university.
Isn't it a bit empty?
Well, there are some things missing.
A pull-up bar, a safe...
There is only one bed.
Well... that's all we need.
Just to kiss.
Lower.
The perfect kiss...
in our perfect apartment.
Well, we can slowly decorate it.
Though it seems a bit risky.
I'm not sure my mother will allow it.
-She doesn't have to find out.
-How won't she find out?
If I don't take the campus dorm,
where will I tell her I live?
Live?
That's not what you meant.
This is so embarrassing.
Fuck, I'm an idiot.
I am barely 18. What was I thinking?
I don't know what I was thinking.
Please don't look at me.
I don't know what I wanted.
I've already accepted a car and
that's enough contradictions for one day.
I am an asshole, man.
You stressed me out
with the flying solo thing,
and I wanted to keep her close.
But I'm not sure
I'm ready to live together.
I was so happy. I lost it.
Girl, I swear romantic love
is a dangerous trap.
I'm telling you.
Look at my Prince Charming
tossing back Black Russians.
And with no remorse
for bailing out on me at my graduation.
I really want to live with her.
But, if I think twice,
I get stressed as shit.
Want to talk about stress?
Living with contradictions is fucked up.
How much does her outfit cost?
The dress, the shoes, the accessories...
Three thousand euros?
How can you think about that
while she makes out with someone else?
That's for bailing out on me.
What was I thinking?
My mother has always taught me
not to depend on any man.
Yeah, well, and for me not to depend
on certain men.
Similar.
I cannot offer her a future
with that standard of living, man.
-Money isn't important.
-Until you don't have it.
But, anyway, you wouldn't know.
-I'm in no mood for your crap right now.
-Nor am I for yours.
Asshole.
My father just bought a private jet,
and he won't even let me
take him out for dinner.
He makes me feel as if I were rubbing
the money in his face or something.
Well, maybe instead of taking him
to posh restaurants,
you could bring dinner over to the garage.
Are you shitting me?
Girl, you grew up with Nick.
You're like his sister.
But I respect him, unlike you.
Please help me understand him.
I swear I saw fear in his eyes yesterday.
It's the whole thing
about his mother abandoning him.
He's that simple.
Listen, he's crazy about you,
but it'll always be hard for him to commit
because he's afraid of being abandoned.
That's really deep, dude.
Thanks.
MOM
Well, it seems like Jenna is bi now.
It's the Black Russians.
She won't remember tomorrow.
Why? What's in them?
No one knows.
Nobody has managed
to remember the ingredients.
Well, then...
to oblivion.
To oblivion.
Look, you each have a study.
-This one and this one.
-How cool.
And look at your bedroom. It is so big.
What do you think?
With that amount,
I could rent four for myself, Mom.
Well, yes.
But, at your age, it is better to share.
Wow, this is lavish, isn't it?
What do you think?
-Hi. Good morning.
-Good morning.
I thought summer was never going to end.
Me neither.
-What school are you coming from?
-Saint Marie.
-So are we.
-Really?
Yes. Well, her.
Have you met?
What? I don't think so.
Well, we got here last year.
We weren't here last year.
We took a sabbatical year.
It was two.
Yeah, two.
She never liked humanities,
and now she wants to study philology.
Well, it's perfect, isn't it?
Shall we keep it?
I love it.
I'm Noah. Pleased to meet you.
Briar. My name is Briar.
Did you want to see me?
Come in, please. Nick, look.
This is Sofía Zabala.
She'll help you with your internship.
She is our new junior recruit,
fresh out of Harvard.
Zabala. Are you the minister's daughter?
I am here on my own merits. How about you?
You were at one of her birthdays
when you were little.
I don't know if you remember her.
No. I remember her sister
with eyes... like...
Strabismal?
Yes. And one of those old braces, right?
-Yes.
-I don't have any sisters.
She was you.
Two direct hits.
Be careful with her.
She's going to be a great lawyer.
You won't hold it against me, right, Sof?
First, my name is Sofía, not Sof.
Second, I know your reputation,
so don't stare at my ass.
Stuck up.
Hello, Freckles.
So Nick finally has
an apartment, doesn't he?
Yes, so I've heard.
Is it nice?
I wouldn't know. I haven't been there.
Listen.
I know this year was hard for you.
-What Dad did was awful.
-I'm getting burned.
You're leaving for college in two weeks.
I think it's time for you and me to talk.
-I don't want to talk about that.
-But I do.
You know perfectly well how hard it's been
for me to fit into this family.
You can't imagine the comments
I have to hear because I married Will.
-Sure, Mom.
-They think I'm only after his money.
And now you do this.
Have you been spying on me?
Not me. Some paparazzi.
Thank God Will managed to stop it.
Can you imagine the headlines?
"First the mother, and now the daughter,
after the Leisters' money."
And that could make
the holding's stock plummet, right?
I'll be more careful.
But I'm 18. Okay, Mom?
Yes. I was also of age
when I met your father,
when I thought
he was the right person for me.
Nick is not like Dad.
Yeah. I know.
But I think he could hurt you too.
Do you really think he's given up
the illegal fights and races?
I trust him.
Because I know he loves me.
Does he? Are you sure?
And I love him.
Not under my roof.
-Hi.
-It's done.
I told my father
I'm not going back to San Francisco.
-What did he say?
-I think he was expecting it.
Are you sure?
I just don't want you to take
a step backward for me.
Absolutely not.
The only thing is I have to share
my office with another intern.
Is she nice?
Well...
And pretty?
No way.
She is crossed-eyed and her feet stink.
Hey, we'll see each other later?
Later?
I am busy later. I have to...
I don't think I can.
I have... I have to work.
I have to split up the work.
I'll switch to voice call.
Hey, I miss you.
I miss you too.
My sister.
I love you.
Me too.
We are a very close-knit family.
Noah.
Come on! Everyone out. The party's over!
Scram! Come on! Everybody out!
Here, let me take it.
Leave the glasses here, okay?
Come on! Out!
I'm so sorry, really.
I didn't have your contact info
to ask for permission.
-It's okay.
-I'm really sorry, okay?
Hey! Off you go. Go fuck in your own home.
Get out. Come on!
I'll pick everything up.
I know this is no excuse, but they told me
you weren't coming until next week.
I know. It's just...
Things have been a bit rushed.
Come on. It's okay.
There you go. Tequila.
I can't see people suffer.
Because life is too wonderful
to waste it on sorrow.
You see,
I have not always thought that way.
Sometimes you find assholes
that make you do crazy stuff.
But, anyway, that was a long time ago,
and it's forgotten now.
Sorry.
I was looking for my jacket.
-This one?
-Yes.
Thank you.
Are you okay?
Ignore him. He's the neighbor.
He's studying psychology.
I'll just pretend I didn't see that.
Michael.
Noah. Pleased to meet you.
And he's doing
an internship in our college.
As a counselor.
So if you ever need anything...
He's really nice.
-Ciao.
And he looks really nice.
Here. Cheers.
Excuse me. Your ex-wife called again.
It's the fifth time this week.
Today, she asked for Nick.
Don't put her through. You know.
-Please.
-All right.
I've reconsidered it.
I'll help with the Ortega case.
Too bad. Templeton for me.
Hi, Freckles.
How was the night with the intern?
Well, she's really a tough nut to crack.
And are her feet really stinky?
And her breath.
It seems like you were right.
There is chemistry between them.
You had a really good idea.
-Talk to me, Luca.
-Listen carefully.
There might be an opportunity
to save the garage.
Run! Pass it! Amazing! And now...
Wow! You can do it!
Can't you tackle me?
You go right, and I go left, okay?
And that's it.
Ready.
-Sister sandwich!
-Yay!
Tickles! Tickles!
-Bye, my love.
-Bye.
Bye, sweetie.
Go in, sweetie.
Hi, son.
Let's go.
I need to talk to you.
How dare you use Maggie
to get close to me?
You won't answer my calls.
I have no other option.
-We have nothing to talk about.
-Just a minute.
"A minute."
That is 60 seconds more
than what you have ever given me.
It's not what you think.
Listen to me, please.
Relax.
I hadn't seen her in years.
How can a mother disappear like that?
Maybe there is something we don't know.
Is it so easy
to forget someone you have loved?
My love.
Where are you going?
I still owe you that kiss, don't I?
You mean--
What is happening here?
Wasn't I supposed
to be taking care of you?
If you want, it's your turn next time.
Hey. No pressure, okay?
I still need to pass the written exam.
I didn't know that the masculine G-spot
was called H-spot.
-Do you know why they call it G-spot?
-It's G for "Goddamn." Fuck!
Nicholas Leister,
you know I don't like hickeys.
You have a hickey? Where?
Listen, it's not funny, okay?
I hate being marked. I am not a cow, Nick.
You aren't?
This specimen is property
of Leister Ranch. No way, all right?
Aren't you exaggerating
just a tiny little bit?
You think?
Would you like to be marked?
-You're going to freak out.
-No, okay?
No. No.
You're going to stay still.
YES, FRECKLES
And this one with permanent marker. Yes.
YOU ARE MINE
Ta-da!
So this is your mansion.
Hey, what's up?
It is not to your liking, milord?
Listen, Lion.
Yes, you have to come see this.
It doesn't smell like posh perfume.
It smells more like a sweaty sock.
I'm about to puke.
I haven't eaten anything the whole trip.
I bet these students don't even
have a sandwich in the fridge.
Exactly what I said,
not even a damn sandwich.
Hi.
This is my roommate, Briar.
Rick, right?
-Nick.
-That's it. Nick.
It's so late, so...
-Leaving already?
-Yes.
It's your first day of college tomorrow.
You need to sleep.
Okay. Do you want me to call you a cab?
Esteban is picking me up. He's on his way.
Something troubling you, sir?
Do you remember Briar?
Briar? Yes, of course.
Poor girl. That wasn't okay.
Where did she end up?
I know, Jenna, but I'm not going
to answer to my mom.
I'll call her later.
It's Lion, sir.
-Fuck, my phone.
-Here.
I have been calling for an hour.
Where are you, bro?
What's wrong?
I fucked up man. I fucked up, man!
Thank you. You can go home.
-You're bleeding!
-No, it's nothing, Nick.
I cut myself opening this fucking package.
What's this?
My brother told me not to open it
and to bring it to that spot.
But you opened it.
I wanted to make sure that it was
something else.
I don't know,
a package with phones, with caviar--
Caviar? How can you be so dumb?
Give it to me.
No! Don't touch it.
Easy. Nobody will know.
Cocaine.
Shit, I knew it. I fucking knew it!
You're an asshole!
If you needed bread,
why didn't you ask me?
Because I don't want
your charity. I told you.
I have no other option, right?
I have to go in there and deliver it.
Those guys are real gangsters.
I may never come out.
I promised Noah I'd stay out of trouble.
Okay.
See you, bro.
Hi, handsome.
Why don't you buy me a drink?
I'm sorry.
Hey, what are you doing, man?
If my girlfriend wants a drink,
you buy her one. Period.
Okay. I'm not looking for trouble.
Here. Order whatever you want.
I'm going to the bathroom.
He says he's with him.
Hello, bro.
Any other family members or...
Excuse me.
I couldn't find you, dude.
Look who we have here.
Nicholas Leister himself
and his little bitch.
Ronnie?
Sorry, I thought you were the bastard--
-It's his brother.
-What a coincidence.
When I tell Ronnie,
he's going to really enjoy it.
Yeah, I also enjoy remembering him.
Because he's still in jail, correct?
Maybe you can enjoy his company soon.
They reduced his sentence.
It seems the poor guy was gagged.
He was just another one
of your father's victims.
Like you.
Anyway, if they don't bring him to trial
before a year has passed,
they'll have to let him go.
I'll be here.
In the meantime, let's do business, right?
It's open.
Seriously?
Didn't they tell you not to open it?
The guy who gave it to me
was not a big talker.
There are 100 grams missing.
That's normal.
If everyone wants a taste, in the end...
One hundred grams
was just an example, huh?
Are you saying
we're trying to swindle you?
Depends on the price.
100 grams, 10,000 euros.
-I thought it was coke, not plutonium.
-It's uncut, sunshine.
Wait, what's happening?
I'm not going to get paid?
-I won't leave without my money, okay?
-Relax.
-You will get what you deserve.
-Let's all calm down, okay?
-The ATM will only give me 3,000.
-I don't want your money.
But I do.
Three from you...
and three from her.
March, ladies.
Who can take care of them for 6,000 euros?
Dude, for that bread, I'll do it myself.
Go.
Hey, handsome. Where were you?
I ordered you a gin and tonic.
So you see my girl is legit.
It doesn't have cucumber.
No. It was for me,
and I want it with cucumber.
She wants it with cucumber.
I won't allow you to hurt my man.
Much less call me a bitch.
No way, Sof. We cannot accept that.
They didn't find the drugs.
So, if you don't talk, neither will they.
-They wanted to fucking kill us.
-Let it be.
If it's just a fight, I'll get you out
this afternoon. I promise.
-Good morning, Sofía.
-Good morning, boss.
Don't let my father find out, please.
You owe me one.
Thank you, Sof. For real.
-Hey, coming up?
-Yes.
Yes?
The police were really nice.
They brought us to our car.
Juan Luis and Paula. Right?
Come on, Freckles.
Nick's gang
against Ronnie's gang. Seriously?
I told you this was Luca's doing.
So that's how you make the money
for your races.
I'm not a fool. I don't need the money.
No, you do it for the fun of it.
-That was low.
-I am really fucking pissed.
I missed my first day of college.
You do realize
you started the fight, don't you?
-Did you have a better plan?
-No. I'm just surprised.
I collect contradictions.
Do you think it doesn't fucking hurt me?
They could have killed you, Nick.
They can't get me away
from you that easily.
Loving you is the hardest thing
I've ever done.
Loving you is the most beautiful thing
You're a brownnoser.
Why did you bring me here?
Because now it's your turn
to save someone's life.
ANIMAL SHELTER
Do you really think this is a good idea?
I'm more a dog person than a cat person.
-Don't say that in front of N.
-N?
Yes. N from Noah, N from Nick.
-That's so cheesy.
-Tough luck.
-Ciao, Michael.
-Ciao, Noah.
He's Briar's friend.
Listen, does this Briar
know about the cat?
Yes, she loves animals.
-She doesn't look like it.
-So what's your issue with her?
-Nothing. She just gives me bad vibes.
-Sure.
Because she's the first girl who doesn't
make eyes at you, and you can't stand it?
No, that's not it.
We just don't know her and...
Why? Did she say something?
She just told me she had
a car accident with her boyfriend
in an illegal race, so maybe you know him.
No. It must have been
when I lived in Mexico.
He was driving.
She was in the hospital for two months
and, when she got out,
he had another girl.
Can you imagine? What a douche.
Now that you mention it,
it does sound familiar.
Like she went crazy
and started to stalk him.
She didn't tell me that.
What I do know is that he disappeared,
as if the earth had swallowed him up.
I'm not coming in.
She's not here, okay?
She's at a Pilates class.
Which means we have an hour
for just the two of us.
I don't want to fuck, really.
You use a lot of swear words, you know?
-Because I'm an ex-convict now.
-Really?
Yes.
And when was the last time
you touched a woman?
No, no.
Do you know I was in France?
Do you want to know what I learned there?
Mr. Nick Leister. I love you, my love.
I love you too.
Show me your baguette.
Yes. Yes.
Don't stop on my account, okay?
I bought this shirt
and wanted to cut the label.
Christ, that was scary.
-Hey, what she had on her wrist was...
-Yes.
That guy must have done something more
than just dump her because...
-Fuck!
-Careful. Damn it.
Little one.
Listen.
Why don't you help me
find furniture for my apartment?
You can come with N and stay until...
I mean, as long as you need.
As long as I need.
Okay, fine.
You can stay for the whole school year.
I really don't mind.
Thank God you don't mind.
Nick, I haven't yet gathered the strength
to go home and grab all my stuff,
and I wanted to do it this week,
so don't mess with my plans, okay?
You're really something, Freckles.
Nick.
The cat.
There you go.
He's so mean.
First, he hurts your paw,
and then he forgets you even exist.
I'm so glad you're with me in linguistics.
I cannot stand the professor!
I don't know. I like him.
Do you know what major you'll choose?
No, not yet. I have doubts.
Michael is fully booked,
but I'm sure he'll find a spot for you
Anyway, think it through and let me know.
-This is your chance.
-See you next week.
Hi. Can I help you?
-No.
-Only her.
I'll see you later at home.
Come in.
Jenna?
I thought you'd take longer
to recognize me.
Noah let me borrow her clothes.
-What are you doing here?
-Do you like my new look?
I'm not wearing anything underneath.
You're not wearing underwear?
Yes, but I'm not wearing anything
under my underwear.
I really wanted to say that.
Since they let you go,
you haven't left the garage.
Jenna, forgive me for... I'm sorry.
I know.
I know, but promise you won't do
any more dumb stuff for money.
-Okay.
-Please.
-No races either.
-No, none.
Lion, I don't want to lose you.
Wait. Let's do that later.
I brought a romantic dinner.
Caviar for starters.
And, to finish up, oysters
and an Olivier, the best French champagne.
Your mother has a sister
who looks just like her.
Hi, Noah!
Hey, do you have a visitor?
I won't bother you.
No, she came to see you.
-Anabel, it's been a pleasure to meet you.
-Same thing, sweetie.
You have my phone if you need me.
Ciao.
It's a small world.
I actually know her parents and then--
What are you doing here?
Maggie tells me great things about you.
Listen, if this is about Nick,
just talk to him, all right?
I have tried everything, Noah.
You're my last chance.
Let's do one thing.
As proof of good faith, I'll let Maggie
spend a whole week with Nick.
That's blackmail.
Sweetie, you had better pray
you don't have to see me blackmail anyone.
Now it's a threat.
You're clever, Noah. Think about it.
Nick needs help.
Are you sure
you don't want to know the truth?
I only care about Nick's truth.
Because the Leisters never lie, right?
By the way, do you know how long your mom
and Will have known each other?
Call me when you're ready.
Hi, Morti, you're very elegant
for a Tuesday, aren't you?
-Can you help me with the boxes?
-I'm sorry, Noah. I can't right now.
Noah.
Hi, Noah! Come in.
Look, this is Alejo Zabala, his wife,
Maite, and their daughter, Sofía,
Nick's office mate.
Pleased to meet you.
So you're the one with stinky feet.
And breath.
I can see you also have sweaty hands.
A pleasure.
I'm sorry. She got us out of trouble.
I had to return the favor.
You're not staying for dinner,
are you, darling?
And then Nick chose the Ortega case
because he thought
it was the Ortegas in A Coruña.
Seriously.
Sofía had the advantage, didn't she?
No, Sofía,
tell them about the arsonist, please.
We decided to build a small scale model
of the explosive device.
Sofía thought that,
instead of us having to prove
that the device worked,
they had to prove that it didn't.
In legal jargon, it's known
as shifting the burden of proof.
Precisely.
And Sofía whispers, "Shift the burden."
And, of course, what did I do?
He changed the terminals
in the battery and it exploded.
He shifted the burden!
I was very nervous. It was our first case.
The day they work together
on something serious,
they're going to be unstoppable.
Work together or whatever else happens.
Sorry.
Hey, Will, can you imagine?
-What would that make us? In-laws, right?
-Yes.
-In-laws!
-Precisely.
Well, come on. There's no hurry.
Let's not pressure them, okay?
Let them go at their own pace.
And you, Noah, how's school?
College. I'm in college now.
How is it to work for the city council?
He's the Minister of Justice now, my dear.
Congratulations.
Do you remember the university dorms?
The good old times.
No, back then...
Shut up!
I'm living in a university apartment,
but Nick wants me to go live with him.
What do you think about that, Mom?
What the hell is wrong with your daughter?
The kidnapping was a year ago.
Excuse her,
her father died a year ago today.
Wow, shit.
Yes, and she hasn't stopped
having nightmares ever since.
Nightmares?
I've never noticed anything.
Do you sleep with her?
They're a very close-knit family.
I'm so dumb.
I forgot.
It's okay.
You had other things on your mind.
Noah, that's not true.
It really isn't true.
Our parents have set us up.
You think this is normal?
Sofía is just an obnoxious social climber.
Yeah, I saw her climb
all the way to nibble your ear.
She was telling me
how good you and I are together.
-Sure.
-Why don't you trust me?
I trust you.
I don't doubt that she was cross-eyed
and knock-kneed when she was 12.
I wanted to spare you the jealousy.
Thank you so much, huh? Thank God.
You make me look like a baby in front
of her, as if I needed protection.
No, it doesn't matter. They're right.
You make a great couple.
There's nothing between us.
Listen, I really mean it, Nick Leister.
One more lie, and it's over.
So, if you have anything to confess to me,
the moment is now.
There is nothing else.
You know?
With every lie you just prove to me
that you're the one who doesn't trust me.
It's as if you always needed an excuse
to keep your distance.
Deep inside, you don't want me
to come live with you.
-Noah, you know I love you.
-Yeah.
My father also loved me once.
YOUR ABSENCE WILL FOLLOW ME
WHILE I SLEEP
You got the tattoo
with the knot because of him?
Why?
He tried to kill you.
You did it for your mother, didn't you?
Why, if she abandoned you?
You know?
When you tie someone up too tight,
they either get hurt trying to break free
or remain trapped forever.
What are we doing, Nick?
Do we stay tied up in our knots
or do we face the truth
even though it might hurt us?
I'm fed up
with having other people decide for me.
It's over.
I'm going to be brave
and find out what is happening to us.
-Relax. There's nobody here.
-So many works of art.
Thor! My dear! Did you miss me?
Do they have you
taking care of the museum?
It might be better if I go.
Don't worry. I'll wait here.
The drawer in the middle
has a false bottom.
You'll see the lawsuit
where I asked for Nick's custody.
ANABEL GRASON SEEKS CUSTODY
OF NICHOLAS LEISTER
And the withdrawal they made me sign
after the blackmail, of course.
You don't know Grandpa Andrew
and his legion of lawyers.
He hates his son, Will,
because he's not like him,
but his grandson is a different story.
He's his heir.
He would never
have allowed me to take him.
Yes, I was unfaithful
to Will and my new husband.
Grandpa found out
and used it to take Nick away from me.
It's unfair...
because before that, Will was already
having an affair with your mother.
It's such a shame
I didn't find out earlier.
"Anti-wrinkle," so cheap.
Pink toothbrush. White toothbrush.
PHOTO
Ready?
Did you find everything?
The truth always hurts.
Believe me, I fought
for Nick's custody with all I had.
I just want you to give him this letter.
Everything is explained there.
I don't know what's worse,
that he hates you
or that he hates his family.
That is his decision to make.
If he finds out I helped you,
he will never forgive me.
You don't have to give it to him, Noah.
Just make sure he finds it and reads it.
What ice cream do you want?
Her parents.
Do you know they're getting a divorce?
What?
Her father has hired Roca as his lawyer.
He told me.
They're going to crush Anabel.
Be careful. I'm sure she's scheming.
Sofía! Today is your lucky day.
-Jenkins is in surgery. Peritonitis.
-Poor thing.
The Rogers case is lost,
but it will teach you a lot.
The black one, please.
-When is the hearing?
-The day after tomorrow.
You have 48 hours to prepare.
-But it's in London?
-Yes.
It would be your first big case.
What do you say?
You can count on me.
Hello.
Hi, Freckles.
How are you? What are you doing here?
Nothing. I wanted to see Maggie
before she left.
She went out for ice cream with Esteban.
Can you give me five minutes?
What is that?
It's my mother's handwriting.
Who brought this?
A messenger just gave it to me.
I left it on the table.
It must have fallen.
Do you want me to read it?
It must be important, Nick.
Do me a favor.
Get rid of it.
You look very pretty.
I didn't know blue roses existed.
-It wasn't necessary.
-Yes, it was.
After the ambush the other day
with the minister,
I owed you a romantic dinner.
As long as no confetti falls from the sky.
There is a surprise, but it's not that.
What is it?
YOU ARE MINE
-No.
-Yes.
Don't fuck with me.
What is it? You don't like it?
You thought I was going to like it?
I wasn't letting
your love letter disappear.
Well, that and that it was
a permanent pen.
But a tattoo is for life, Nick.
It's crazy, really.
-You'll be sorry.
-I didn't do anything new, Noah.
I've had you tattooed on my skin
for a long time.
I want to be honest with you.
We're going to London for a few days.
"We?"
Sofía and I.
Everyone thinks
the case is lost, but if we win,
it might open up many doors for us.
I'm really happy for both of you.
I have been thinking and...
maybe honesty is overrated.
Some truths are just too complicated.
I agree with you.
You think being an adult
is doing whatever you want,
but it actually means
to know what you have to do.
Promise you'll stay here
until I come back.
You know? I have a weird feeling.
As if this were a goodbye.
I'm only going for a few days.
Yeah.
So, why did you tear up the letter?
Because I don't want to know anything.
I thought you were going to accompany me
in untying our knots.
It's my decision,
and you have to respect it.
I guess it's for the best.
Hi, Mom.
So this is the apartment.
Will always says that all a Leister needs
is a safe and a pull-up bar.
I was only staying for a few days.
At the dinner with the minister,
you crossed a red line I won't tolerate.
You don't know how hard it is
to manage emotions
when you have to hide them from others.
Or do you?
I've tried not to meddle
in your relationship with Nick--
Bullshit!
You sent him to San Francisco
for a whole year to keep us apart.
That's not true.
It was just a coincidence.
Sure, as coincidental
as the trip we took to Europe
when Nick was coming home
for a few days, right?
You even sent him to London
with Sofía. Well played.
Maybe this time it will work.
I don't care. I won't let you live
with someone at 18.
I didn't say I would,
but it's my life, Mom.
You have to let me make my own mistakes.
Perfect. But if you do,
forget about university.
Now you're the manager of William's money.
And you will sacrifice your future?
Do you think he'd do the same for you?
I don't know.
Noah, I have always believed in you,
since you were a child,
since I took you in my arms
to that hospital
while you were bleeding out.
I saw strength in your eyes.
That will to live told me you'd always
achieve everything you wanted.
I only had to give you opportunities.
Tell me where I've failed you,
what I've done wrong.
-Can you explain it to me?
-Can you explain to me where you were...
that night while my father
was stabbing me with a knife?
Who were you sleeping with
at a luxury hotel, Mom?
I know how much you suffered with Dad.
That's why I've never wanted to hurt you.
But now that I know this,
I feel free to love whoever I want.
Unconditionally.
Some paparazzi took photos of you?
Yes, Granddad. It sucks.
Noah prefers to avoid public places.
In the end, you end up meeting less often.
I love it when you tell me things.
That woman is perfect.
And you wouldn't have to hide.
Granddad, I wanted to talk to you
about one thing.
Do you remember Briar?
I took care of her,
so she wouldn't bother you again.
-Forget her.
-Something else happened, didn't it?
Why did you ask me
to disappear for a while?
Look, Nick, one day,
when you are in charge of the corporation,
you'll have to deal with all the trouble.
But, until then, let me take care of this.
If there's anything else, I want to know.
Briar was committed for two years.
She wasn't well before she met you.
So don't torture yourself.
It has nothing to do with you.
Still in my grandfather's apartment?
Yes
Take care of N
Noah! I'm cooking a stew.
Would you like some?
No, thanks. I already ate.
-Great. I'll leave some in a Tupperware.
-Okay.
Wow. It looks like Nick
has her wrapped around his finger,
doesn't he, little one?
That's how he is.
One word and he puts you on cloud nine...
or buried five meters underground.
But we won't let him win. Right, Briar?
It's us who ought to bury him
five meters underground.
No, please.
Not another dinner with our parents.
-Poor Noah.
-She was so jealous.
Hey, is it true you asked her to live
with you even though she's only 18?
Maybe you're the one who's jealous.
Come on, Sof. I'm not
your typical controlling boyfriend.
I'm just saying that having you
as a boyfriend would be last on my list.
Yeah, because you're an iceberg,
pretty girl.
The only thing you're capable of loving
is your job.
You're an idiot.
-Sorry, I just wanted to mess with you.
-Sure.
I know that's not how you are.
Listen, Nick, do you love Noah?
Madly.
Look, Nick, a piece of advice.
At least with Noah,
try not to do things without thinking.
In my experience,
when you have a relationship
that so many people want to destroy,
it usually doesn't end up well.
The sentence.
-No.
-Yes!
-Yes?
Where's the champagne?
Noah!
Come on! Go.
-Three!
-The boys win.
Very good. Then the boys get to drink.
-Not him.
-No?
-No.
-He's underage.
Yes.
-Listen.
-He wants to.
Oh, my God. Everything is spinning.
Well, I'm going to bed.
-No.
-I can't believe you.
I'm exhausted.
-N holds up better than you.
-Ciao.
-Do you know how to get there?
-Hey, shut up.
-Don't get lost.
-Hey, screw you.
She's going to get lost.
She's really drunk, my goodness.
Well, she'll find her way.
Oh, God.
Everything is spinning for me too.
If I close my eyes, I get really dizzy,
so, let's leave it for another day.
-Sure.
-All right.
It was fun.
Yes. You and Briar are a very funny pair.
I laughed a lot. And I needed it.
I'm glad.
See you on Tuesday.
All right.
Are you Nick?
Michael. Pleased to meet you.
Excuse me.
What was that moment?
-What moment?
-That moment.
There was no moment.
You'll see him on Tuesday?
He's the school counselor,
and he's helping me to find an internship.
I want to quit the restaurant.
So what were you doing? Updating your CV?
Lower your voice. Briar is sleeping.
You promised you'd stay in the apartment.
I argued with my mother,
and I didn't feel comfortable.
And I find you with this guy.
I argued with my mother!
Do you give a shit?
We won the case. Do you give a shit?
-I argue with my father too, okay?
-About business.
I'm the one who is
under pressure for us not to be together.
They treat you like a god, including
offering you Sofía on a silver platter.
"Silver platter."
Sof is going to laugh.
You laugh a lot together, right?
You and Sof.
Look, Nick, I have been thinking,
and I think we should take a break.
Let's see if I understand
this space-time loop.
That moment earlier
has turned into a break now?
We are constantly lying to each other.
You don't trust me, and I don't trust you.
And we don't even have fun anymore.
You have been drinking. Sleep it off.
Yeah, right?
It's better to ignore what I'm saying.
Do you want me to write it down for you
or will you tear that up too?
Nick, I mean it.
This is not working. We're growing apart.
I have been offered a position in London.
In London. Congratulations.
I have a week to answer.
So you have a week to make up your mind.
An ultimatum.
Awesome.
The annual company gala is in a week,
so if you decide to come this time,
we'll talk there.
We'll talk there.
What are you wearing, dude?
What's wrong? You've never seen me
in my work clothes before?
These are what my work clothes look like.
What brings you here?
I'm not sleeping very well lately.
-What's wrong? Rich kid problems?
-Hey, I'm here, all right?
Thank you for honoring me
with your presence. Thanks.
And you got Noah and me in that mess.
That's why the young master
doesn't answer my calls?
I'm not in a good place with Noah,
and I don't want any trouble.
Am I a bad influence on you?
Go back to your bubble then.
I wouldn't want to get it dirty.
This is Italian.
What the fuck is wrong with you?
What's wrong? The garage is sinking.
I can't make ends meet.
or keep up
with my rich girlfriend.
I can't take it anymore!
When I was in Mexico without
a fucking cent, you helped me out.
-Why don't you let me help you now?
-No, bro.
I helped you get back on your feet.
You did the rest.
And that is what I want to do too.
Hey. Hey.
-Hey, bro?
-Not another race.
Come on, brother.
It will be the last one. I swear to you.
-Jenna will kill you.
-No, because I have it all figured out.
The race is the night of the gala, right?
So, while Noah and Jenna get ready,
primp, put on their make-up,
we get ready and leave with some excuse.
We race, and we get back there
before the photocall, bro. Flawless.
We?
Me and my best friend.
No fucking way.
Besides, I don't have a car.
-Ask Mikel to lend it to you.
-I'll pass.
I heard Ronnie is running too.
He's getting out that same day.
You haven't seen that son of a bitch
since he kidnapped Noah.
Tell me you don't want
to send him back to prison.
The sketch with the distribution
of the tables... Don't forget it.
Can you help me with this, please?
-Yes, come in.
-Hey, ma'am.
There is no way
to make this wrinkle go away.
No, one more wrinkle makes no difference.
I didn't mean you, all right?
Hi.
Wow. What's with that tuxedo?
I borrowed it from Nick.
So you do accept gifts from him?
You look very nice.
So do you.
Hey, we're going to head out.
We have to stop by Nick's apartment.
Yeah, I forgot my wallet.
See you at the gala, okay?
Ciao.
I missed you at the pool hall.
-It didn't work out well for you.
-What are you dealing in now?
Tuxedos?
He doesn't make enough at the garage
to bring his mom over from Mexico.
And business is going great for you.
Where is the money
Noah's father promised you
if you helped him kidnap her?
Nick, you don't mind if I race
with your old car, do you?
Enjoy it.
It might be the last time
you use it in years.
Chill, okay? We came here to race.
As soon as we're all here,
we'll set the rules.
We're all here.
The sooner this is over, the better.
We're missing a racer.
No fucking way.
Look at them. Asshole number one
and asshole number two.
Well, you know the circuit.
-You know how this works.
-Hi, guys.
The winner will take
15,000 euros plus bets.
Would you like to bet again, Ronnie?
With you, always.
You must make a complete circuit
and return to the finish line.
It's very dangerous.
And you love danger, don't you, Nick?
You're always playing with fire.
We are ready to cut off the streets,
but remember, if the police show up,
you're on your own.
And there is only money
if you finish the race.
Good luck and may the best one win.
Hi, sweetie pie.
How did you find out about the race?
I put my naked butt on that hood.
Did you think I wouldn't realize?
Do you know how many months
I have to work in the garage
to make what I'll make here?
Sorry, asshole number two.
But if someone
is going to win the race, it's us.
Leave that there.
-What's up? How are you?
-Fine. They're about to start.
Shit.
Accelerate!
All right, girls.
Girls! The joke was fun,
but that's enough.
Do you think we're here for you guys?
Please don't fuck this up.
I need Lion to win.
I'm sorry. I'm very competitive.
And me, as a capitalist copilot,
I don't want to lose the 1,000 euros
from the entry fee.
They told me you don't know
the difference between coke and caviar.
I'll just leave you to your things, boys.
Police? There are some crazy people
racing illegally.
-Shit. Someone snitched on us.
-Fuck.
Police. Open all the roadblocks. Open.
15,000 plus the bets, right?
Is that what our relationship is worth?
-Fucking proud brat.
-I'm losing my focus, Jenna!
That too?
What the fuck are you doing?
Shit!
Reject - Message - Accept
The streets should be cut off.
Leave before there's an accident.
Would it be your first accident, Nick?
Freckles
He and a redhead
had a car crash years ago.
I'll tell you the story one day.
Yeah.
Units two and four,
cut through the next street.
You're in control, huh, blondie?
You owe me a foot massage.
Damn, girl. Shit.
Go! Go!
Fuck!
Fuck! Fuck!
Let's go.
I'm coming for you, blondie.
-Are you okay?
-Yes, just chilling.
Really?
Stop, police. Stop the car!
-You're not angry with me anymore, right?
-No. Angry. Why?
Well, can you move? I need to pass.
-No fucking way.
-He's nuts.
Stop! Stop the car.
-Nothing. They don't fucking listen. Go.
-I'm using the nitro.
Come on, ladies, please. Stop the vehicle.
Come on. Drop it, please.
Fuck, the nitro.
Let's go!
INCOMING CALL
FRECKLES
Asshole number one,
you know why we're here, don't you?
We'll never have
an opportunity like this one.
Let's make the best of it then,
little sister.
Sister sandwich!
Hey! What are you doing?
What are they doing?
Get off, fucker.
Fuck, my car.
No! No!
Slow down!
We must leave
before the rest of the police arrive.
-Everybody out! Out! Everyone!
-Move! Move!
Nice one, brother.
Out you go. Come on!
Get up!
Better to have it towed away.
-Welcome, Greg.
-Thank you.
-Welcome.
Mr. Tavish.
How are you, Lion?
Have you thought about my offer?
Let's go, Dad.
Thank you for inviting me.
Smile for the cameras.
There's a bastard out there who's going
to really suffer if he sees you.
I hope so.
Nick, over here!
Sofía, please.
A smile, please.
-Jenna, listen to me.
-Leave me alone. I've been a fool.
You have always made me feel guilty
for having money.
-You and your stupid inferiority complex.
-You're right.
But something really weird
happened in that race.
I won, and I didn't feel anything, Jenna.
Do you know what I feel, Lion?
That you don't love me for who I am.
You cannot separate my money
from the person I am.
You're not listening, Jenna.
I won 15,000 euros, and I felt nothing.
I don't feel anything either.
It's over, Lion.
We're done.
When you do things
like that, that's what happens.
-Hello.
I never actually thanked you
for the letter in the office.
I didn't even remember.
-Congratulations on the Rogers case.
-Thank you.
I still can't believe it.
And you're going to London?
Yes. I am.
Enjoy it, okay?
What the hell are you doing here?
I always wanted you
to bring me to the gala, love.
Hey, Nick. How are you?
Why didn't you?
We only dated for a few months
three years ago.
It's pointless for you to chase me.
You are so charming.
It will be a pleasure, Mr. Tavish.
I hope so.
I knew you'd come with her.
I couldn't say no. Her father asked me.
I didn't expect you'd come with Briar.
I couldn't say no either.
The week is already over.
-The day doesn't end until midnight.
-Yeah.
Are you going to London with Sofía?
I have until 12:00 to decide.
You also have time to catch up with Briar.
That's why I brought her along.
You're old friends, aren't you?
By the way, she told me
how the story ended with that boy.
Really heavy stuff.
I'll reserve a dance for you at midnight.
I'm going to leave the garage
to my brother.
Jenna's father offered me
a position at the oil company.
And, so, I will have to start
from the bottom.
Welcome to the Contradiction Club.
If I have to swim in a pool of money
in order to be with Jenna...
I'll make the sacrifice.
Good evening, everyone.
Welcome to this year's gala.
Who would have thought?
Fifty years since Grandpa Andrew
founded his first law firm in London,
then came the insurance company,
the consultancy, and the rest is history.
So we can go sit down,
and I advise you
not to move from your seat
because tonight
is going to be full of surprises.
Isn't that Briar?
What is she doing here?
Stop. I can do it by myself.
My favorite granddaughter.
Hey, excuse me, aren't you--
To the right, man.
It's always through the door on the right.
So where's your friend?
Surprise!
Call security.
I'll leave you alone.
You didn't want to listen to me
the easy way.
Get out.
Nick, calm down. Calm down.
Calm down.
Say whatever you have to
through our lawyers.
I know your game,
and I won't leave you time to plot
and hide everything from Nick again.
Let's go to the garden. You and I alone.
It's either all of us or no one.
Don't even dream about it.
Then let's talk here.
Nick, you need to know
I didn't leave your father.
There was another woman then.
Wasn't there, Rafaella?
You had already met?
Nick! Nick!
I wanted you to stay with me,
but your grandfather prevented it.
-Don't listen to her!
-Enough.
What do you want?
What's that?
A paternity test.
What is it, Will?
It's Maggie.
What's happening with Maggie?
She's my daughter.
Yes. My daughter is a Leister.
That's a lie. Isn't it, Dad?
I always had my doubts about Maggie.
You say this now
that your husband's kicking you out.
I'm not doing this for me.
The swine asked for a paternity test.
And I won't leave my daughter defenseless.
Can it be?
Maybe. In the Bahamas.
Before the divorce.
I loved that vacation.
Get out of here! Get out of here! Out!
How did you get my DNA?
Pink toothbrush.
White toothbrush.
Did you sneak into the mansion?
It was me.
What?
I let her in.
How could you?
What the letter said was real, Nick.
She didn't abandon you.
You brought the letter?
I thought the truth would help you.
Help me do what?
To find out that
my grandfather is a monster?
That my father
has been fooling me my whole life?
That my mother still doesn't love me
and only wants to protect
her daughter's future?
I believed her!
I thought she wanted to win you back.
You helped her, Noah.
Do you know what you've unleashed?
You have ruined all our lives!
Our family's.
Us.
No, not us.
All of this is your fault.
Wait, please.
You knew what I was going to say
at the gala, about Briar, the races.
I didn't mind.
I just wanted us to be brave.
This is your chance to be brave.
And if you don't,
it doesn't really matter.
I love you more than my life,
and I could never abandon you.
This is worse than abandoning.
You stabbed me in the back.
Nick!
Nick.
Are you all right, Miss Noah?
Can I help you?
Everything is over.
Nick, you don't know
how much you're screwing shit up.
Maybe.
But it's my shit.
Nick!
Wait up, brother.
I knew you'd end up finding out.
I didn't want to tell you, but...
they've been hooking up for a while.
You're wrong if you think this hurts me.
You're so dumb, bro!
Why did you kiss Sofía?
Noah fucked things up with my mother.
She deserves it.
Your mother. Always your mother.
You really have a problem, dude.
-You have to grow up.
-Don't lecture me. What about you?
Me? I couldn't even stay angry
at Jenna for half an hour.
I preferred to swallow my pride.
Good for you.
I hope you live happily ever after.
Remember when I told you
they were kids and they would fly away?
Well, they did.
And they've shown us that
they are way more mature than us.
You know?
When Jenna said we were over, I felt...
as if...
as if a huge wave swallowed me up.
Tell me that's not what you felt
when you ended things with Noah.
Why are you doing all this?
Don't waste all your tears, my dear.
You'll have plenty of time to miss him.
Where's Noah?
You're too late, Romeo.
-What did you tell her?
-What do you think?
How wonderful you are.
I'm really sorry about the accident.
I really am.
You didn't even wait for me
to leave the hospital.
You just left me there
with more than 20 fractures.
And you knew how I was.
What do you mean?
Pregnant.
I swear I had no idea.
Don't play dumb.
They told me I lost it in the accident.
But I know it was you.
Your family! The hospital was yours!
Listen, what you're saying
doesn't make any sense, Briar.
But, if you really lost it,
believe me, I'm truly sorry.
Guilt makes you feel better.
Not me.
I need you to pay.
Tell me where the fuck Noah is.
She must be on her way to the apartment.
To slit her wrists. I hope.
Damn.
Noah! Noah!
Noah!
Here. Dry off a bit.
Give me the handbag.
I lost my keys.
Don't worry.
I couldn't sleep.
Forgive me.
I know you only wanted to help me.
I love you
SLIDE TO TURN OFF
Are you okay?
Did something happen?
My God, you're freezing.
I can't talk. Just hug me.
No, thank you.
That's still wet.
Here, put this on.
Ciao.
What have we done, Will?
We ruined everything.
You know that, right?
Whatever happens to them from now on
will be our fault.
YOUR ABSENCE WILL FOLLOW ME
WHILE I SLEEP
Goodbye, Dad.
ALWAYS
NOAH, I WILL ALWAYS BE YOUR
NOAH, I WILL ALWAYS BE
YOUR LIGHT IN THE DARKNESS - NICK